ourtuts.com 2019-12-03

# Privacy Policy - DeliciousThemes

## Who we are

Our website address is: [https://deliciousthemes.com](https://deliciousthemes.com/).

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

### Contact forms

We’re using Contact Form 7 for our contact forms. When you submit a form, the information will be sent to our email address and it will also be stored inside our database as a backup measure.

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### Analytics

We’re using Google Analytics and JetPack for

## Who we share your data with

  * ActiveCampaign, Mailchimp, Drip – we store our users contact details for newsletters, announcements, and value-driven purposes. They can opt-out of these at any time.

## How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

If you’ve subscribed to our email list, the email information is sent to  a third-party email processor.

## Contact information

You can reach us out by email at contact (at) deliciousthemes.com or by submitting a contact form at <https://deliciousthemes.com/contact/>

## Additional information

### How we protect your data

We protect customer data with the following site features:

  * We are entirely using SSL/HTTPS throughout all our sites. This encrypts our user communications with the servers so personal identifiable information is never captured by third parties without authorization.
  * Databases are sanitized before deploying to development or testing environment.

In case of a data breach, System administrators will immediately go through affected areas and will try to restore the information to the previous state.

### What data breach procedures we have in place

If for any reason there is a data breach, we will promptly alert you of such a breach and block all activity to the site until the breach is secured. Once we have alerted you of such a breach, you may request to have any data removed from our site.

### What third parties we receive data from

If you’ve submitted a support ticket, your information can be forwarded to our third-party email provider to ensure we’re providing you a top-notch experience and also value to your business.
